famecrowd.com 2014-02-24

# FameCrowd | The Leader in Social Media Marketing

The team at famecrowd.com considers the security and privacy of its users quite seriously. Therefore, kindly ensure that you read and understand fully your rights and responsibilities during service and site usage.   
**  
1\. Contents of this policy:** This privacy policy fully covers all services provided by famecrowd and in the event  that you need more details or information, kindly contact us at the earliest.  
**2\. Your Information:** If you sign up for an account at famecrowd to make use of a service or a promotion requiring the registration process, we collect personal information from you that may include your name, account password and the email address. In the event you opt for certain services like an advertising program, we may also ask you for payment relevant information like you credit card data which is maintained in an encrypted form stored on secure servers operated by other third parties such as Paypal.com. The information thus provided by you may be combined across various famecrowd services to enhance your site experience and site quality. In any circumstances, we will never share any information given by you with any unauthorized parties.   
**3\. Cookies:** While visiting famecrowd, we may send or point some cookies to your computer or laptop to identify the browser uniquely. This helps us improve the quality of service by remembering user preferences while tracking the usage trends. Famecrowd also uses cookies as a part of its advertising services in order to help publishers and advertisers to serve and manage advertisements on the internet.

**4\. Information Storage:** When you visit famecrowd, our servers automatically records browser information sent from your computer in the form of logs. These logs could include some information pertaining to web requests, IP address, type of browser, language used and the time and date of the request.   
**5\. Communication:** In the event that you send an email to us at famecrowd, we may choose to retain such communications to enable us to process your requests, respond and improve your experience.

**6\. Affiliated Websites/Links/Other websites:** At famecrowd, we may offer certain services in connection to **** other web sites/ links or our affiliated websites in which case the personal information that is on those sites may be sent to famecrowd to enable service delivery. In such cases, these other sites may have different privacy practices and we would like you to go through them.

**7\. Information Sharing:** Famecrowd **** shares personal information with other entities outside of famecrowd only in the following circumstances:

**a.**  When we obtain your consent or opt-in.

**b.**  We may provide information to our affiliated companies, subsidiaries or trusted partners or businesses for the sole purpose of processing it. We ensure that such parties agree to process the required information as per our set instructions and in full compliance to this Privacy Policy in addition to having appropriate security measures in place.

**c.**  When we firmly believe that use, access, disclosure or preservation of said information is necessary to (a) comply with any applicable law, legal process, regulation or an enforceable governmental request, (b) to enforce Terms of Service that can include investigation of violations or potential ones (c) address, detect or prevent fraud, technical or security issues, or (d) protect ourselves against probable harm to rights, safety or property of famecrowd, its users or the public at large as permitted by law. 

**8\. Changes:** This **** Privacy Policy may change or update frequently. However, we will tend not to reduce the ambit of your rights without your explicit consent, and it is expected that the changes will be minor. Regardless, we will regularly post any changes on this page and when we feel that the changes are significant, we issue a prominent notice. In case of any clarifications required, do contact us through this website.

>
